export const resp = {
  questions: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "Whats your name?",
      answer: "Shreyansh",
      offeredRun: 4
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "Whats your hobbies?",
      answer: "Cricket, chess, movie",
      offeredRun: 2
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "Whats your company name?",
      answer: "Mindtree",
      offeredRun: 1
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "Whats your route to office",
      answer: "phase 1",
      offeredRun: 6
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "Whats your age?",
      answer: "27",
      offeredRun: 1
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "Whats your job title?",
      answer: "Module lead",
      offeredRun: 3
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "Whats your age?",
      answer: "27",
      offeredRun: 1
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "Dot Ball",
      answer: "",
      offeredRun: 0
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "Bowled",
      answer: "",
      offeredRun: 0
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "No Ball",
      answer: "",
      offeredRun: 1
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "Wide Ball",
      answer: "",
      offeredRun: 1
    }
  ]
};
